# FATIK OWAIS

# UI/UX Designer



## CONTACT

+92-333-3368701 fatikowais@gmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

2011–2015

NED University - Bachelors in
Computer & Information
Systems Engineering

2009-2011 **D.J Science College** 

1999-2009

**Al-Saqib Public School** 

# **PROFILE**

An artist who uses his technical knowledge to come up with creative solutions to the challanges.

With the goal of creating delightlful experiences for the end user I have a knack for attention to details. I love to play creative role in each step of the product development.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### UI/UX DESIGNER. TEKVARE. 2018-PRESENT

Producing UI of webistes including its imagery and animation

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER. ARPATECH. 2017-2018

Built an API for e-commerce website that lets user visualize their custom design in a realistic 3d representation.

### **BRAND EXECUTIVE. ARPATECH. 2017**

Managed and worked alongside marketing team to design products and to keep their brand identity consistent.

## CREATIVE MANAGER. HAYTHAMS AD AGENCY. 2016

Managed and worked with a team of graphic designers, animators, and videographers.

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

## ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

Iconography, illustration, logo, vectorization, scene design

#### ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

Website visualization, UI components design, photo retouch & editing, animated GIFs

## ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS

2d animation videos, UI animation, motion graphics

#### SKETCH FOR MAC

Responsive prototypes, mobile apps UI/UX, customer journey design & rapid prototyping

### WEB APP DEVELOPMENT

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS(beginner level), Bootstrap, Foundation,